He'll always be mommy's little mutant.
The Suckling is a horror film directed by Francis Teri.
A woman goes to a back alley abortion clinic, only to have her aborted fetus
attack her, her boyfriend, and everyone else at the clinic.
Axel, played by Frank Rivera.
Candy, played by Marie Michaels.
Sherman, played by Gerald Preger.
Girl, played by Lisa Petruno.
Big Mama, played by Janet Sovey.
Bill, played by Tim Martin Crouse.
The Suckling (also known as Sewage Baby) is a 1990 American horror film directed by Francis Teri and
starring Frank Rivera (under the pseudonym Frank Reeves), Marie Michaels, and Michael Gingold.
The film explores themes of mutation, brothel,
abortion, toxic waste, embarrassed.
The tone is dark.